<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".HomeActivity">

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView2"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:scaleType="fitXY"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:srcCompat="@drawable/backgroundforarticles" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/Article6Title"
        android:layout_width="362dp"
        android:layout_height="101dp"
        android:layout_marginStart="8dp"
        android:layout_marginLeft="8dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="40dp"
        android:background="#00297E03"
        android:fontFamily="@font/firasans_bold"
        android:padding="10sp"
        android:text="@string/Article6_Title"
        android:textColor="#FFFFFF"
        android:textSize="32sp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="@+id/imageView2"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.39"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.0"
        tools:visibility="visible" />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView2"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="30dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="@+id/imageView2"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.0"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/Article6Title"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="1.0">

        <androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
            android:id="@+id/Article4ConstraintLayout"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView2"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginStart="40dp"
                android:layout_marginLeft="40dp"
                android:fontFamily="@font/firasans_bold"
                android:text="By Nina Wang"
                android:textColor="#FBFBFB"
                android:textSize="24sp"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

            <ImageView
                android:id="@+id/imageView"
                android:layout_width="404dp"
                android:layout_height="340dp"
                app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
                app:srcCompat="@drawable/stress"
                tools:layout_conversion_absoluteHeight="352dp"
                tools:layout_conversion_absoluteWidth="409dp" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/Article6Text"
                android:layout_width="0dp"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginStart="40dp"
                android:layout_marginLeft="40dp"
                android:layout_marginEnd="40dp"
                android:layout_marginRight="40dp"
                android:background="#00297E03"
                android:fontFamily="@font/firasans_regular"
                android:lineSpacingExtra="8sp"
                android:padding="10sp"
                android:text="At times, it may feel like there’s nothing you can do about your stress. In reality, the simple act of realizing that you’re in control of your own life is another step towards managing stress. You can do this by taking charge of your emotions, your lifestyle, and the way you deal with problems. No matter how stressful life may seem, there are always steps that you can take in order to relieve the pressure.   Tip #1: Identify the source(s) of stress in your life. While it is easy to pinpoint major stressors in life, such as moving, exams, and relationships, identifying chronic stressors may prove to be more difficult. Don’t overlook how much your daily thoughts and behaviors can contribute to your stress levels.   Look closely at your everyday habits and excuses: Do you explain your stress as temporary, even though you can’t remember the last time you took a break? Do you define stress as an integral part of your home/work life, or as a part of your personality? Do you place blame on others or outside events as a factor of your stress, or do you view stress to be normal?  Your stress levels will remain unchanged unless you accept responsibility for the role you play in creating it.   Tip #2: Practice the 4 A’s of stress management.  Avoid unnecessary stress -Learn how to say “no.”  Know your limits and stick to them. Resist the pressure to have to say “yes” to everything, regardless of whether you can handle it or not.  -Avoid people who stress you out. Limit the amount of time you spend with people who cause unwanted stress in your life, or end the relationship completely.  -Take control of the environment. If you get anxiety from watching the daily news, turn off the TV. If going to a crowded mall to purchase items makes you stressed, resort to online shopping.   Alter the situation -Be willing to compromise. When you ask someone to change their behavior, you must be willing to do the same. Finding a middle ground may require some bending from both sides.  -Create a balanced schedule. All work and no play = major burnout. Try to find a balance between your social life, your worklife, and your personal life.      Adapt to the stressor -Look at the big picture. How important is the stressor in the grand scheme of things? Will it affect you in a couple months, a couple years? Take perspective of the situation, and if it’s not a big deal, focus your energy into something more worthwhile.  -Adjust your standards. Perfectionism may lead to unnecessary stress. Stop setting yourself up for disappointment and failure by demanding perfection. Start setting realistic goals for yourself and others.   Accept the things you can’t change -Look for the upside. When facing hardships and setbacks, look at them as opportunities for personal growth. -Learn to forgive. Accept the fact that we all live in an imperfect world, and everyone makes mistakes. Free yourself from negative energy by moving on.  -Share your feelings. Expressing your feelings can be incredibly beneficial, so talk to a trusted friend or go to a professional.   Tip #3: Learn to relieve stress in the moment Whether you’re in the middle of a confusing math lesson, or in an argument with a close friend, you’ll need to find ways to relieve your tension in the moment. That’s where quick stress-relief practices come in.   The fastest way to calm down is by using your senses - what you see, hear, feel, taste, and smell - or through soothing movements. Simply by looking at a favorite picture, hugging a pet, or listening to your favorite music, you can relax and focus yourself. The key to quick stress relief, however, is by experimenting and discovering the unique sensory experiences that work for you.    "
                android:textColor="#F0F3F0"
                android:textSize="18sp"
                app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/imageView"
                tools:layout_conversion_absoluteHeight="2811dp"
                tools:layout_conversion_absoluteWidth="369dp" />
        </androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
    </ScrollView>

    <include
        android:id="@+id/include"
        layout="@layout/navigation_bar" />


</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>